pinoyparazzi.com 2019-12-18

# Privacy Policy - Pinoy Parazzi

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletter.

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

 **Cookies And Web Beacons**  
Pinoyparazzi.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on pinoyparazzi.com.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to pinoyparazzi.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, Komli, TribalFusion, Innity.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on pinoyparazzi.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Pinoyparazzi.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You can however opt out of some, but not all, of these cookies in one location at the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out website at www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Pinoyparazzi.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of  such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

 **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy or you wish to unsubscribe from our site and services you may contact us by writing to us at:

contact@pinoyparazzi.com
